Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Farewell.
وداع.
You wretched chrysanthemum spirit,
يا روح الأقحوان البائسة،
trapped for years and still unrepentant.
محاصرون منذ سنوات ولا يزالون غير نادمين.
Shopkeeper Shangguan,
صاحب المتجر شانغجوان،
why won't you ever let me go?
لماذا لن تسمح لي بالذهاب أبدًا؟
Come back.
عد.
The time has come, chrysanthemum spirit.
لقد حان الوقت، يا روح الأقحوان.
I'm sorry
أنا آسف
for startling you.
لتفاجئك.
Who's speaking?
من يتكلم؟
I didn't mean to harm you.
لم أقصد أن أؤذيك.
Would you mind watering me?
هل تمانع في سقيني؟
I am Tao Shi.
انا تاو شي.
Your great kindness,
لطفك العظيم
I shall never forget.
لن أنسى أبدا.
Are you human or ghost?
هل أنت إنسان أم شبح؟
I was human a thousand years ago.
لقد كنت إنسانًا منذ ألف عام.
Benefactor,
فاعل خير،
you need not be afraid.
لا داعي للخوف .
I won't harm you.
لن أؤذيك.
Just call me Dongfang Zhaobai.
فقط اتصل بي Dongfang Zhaobai.
Brother Dongfang.
الأخ دونغفانغ.
Why are you in this monster inn?
لماذا أنت في هذا النزل الوحشي؟
Could it be
هل يمكن أن يكون
you're also here because of an obsession?
أنت هنا أيضًا بسبب هوس؟
I should have vanished a thousand years ago,
كان ينبغي لي أن أختفي منذ ألف عام،
but because of a promise to a friend,
ولكن بسبب وعد لصديق،
therefore,
لذلك،
I had no choice but to remain in this form.
لم يكن أمامي خيار سوى البقاء بهذا الشكل.
Do spirits have friends too?
هل للأرواح أصدقاء أيضاً؟
For a thousand years,
منذ ألف عام،
I've been trapped here by the innkeeper,
لقد تم احتجازي هنا من قبل صاحب النزل،
unable to escape.
غير قادر على الهروب.
I was about to perish,
لقد كنت على وشك الهلاك،
but fortunately,
ولكن لحسن الحظ،
you saved me.
لقد انقذتني.
It's that Shangguan Feiye again.
إنه Shangguan Feiye مرة أخرى.
She truly is a habitual offender,
إنها حقا مجرمة معتادة،
even more frightening than monsters.
أكثر رعبا من الوحوش.
Well,
حسنًا،
never mind, I was just passing by.
لا يهم، لقد كنت أمر فقط.
It was nothing.
لم يكن شيئا.
Don't worry about it.
لا تقلق بشأن هذا
Bye-bye.
وداعا وداعا.
Brother Dongfang.
الأخ دونغفانغ.
Benefactor,
فاعل خير،
may I ask one more favor of you?
هل يمكنني أن أطلب منك خدمة أخرى؟
I'm just an ordinary person.
أنا مجرد شخص عادي.
I really can't help you.
لا أستطيع مساعدتك حقًا.
Please,
لو سمحت،
I beg you.
أرجوك.
You're the only one who can help me here.
أنت الوحيد الذي يمكنه مساعدتي هنا.
Brother Dongfang,
الأخ دونغفانغ،
please drink this wine.
من فضلك اشرب هذا النبيذ.
You will then know what happened that year
وسوف تعرف حينها ما حدث في ذلك العام
and realize
وأدرك
I have not been lying.
لم اكن اكذب.
This is the scene
هذا هو المشهد
of our last encounter.
من لقاءنا الأخير.
Indeed.
بالفعل.
Back then,
في ذلك الوقت،
I was fortunate to meet you,
لقد كنت محظوظا بلقائك،
which inspired me to create this painting.
الذي ألهمني لإنشاء هذه اللوحة.
Your heart guides your brush,
قلبك يرشد فرشاتك،
capturing essence without confusion.
التقاط الجوهر دون ارتباك.
Brother Gao,
الأخ قاو،
your brushwork is truly masterful.
إن عملك بالفرشاة ماهر حقًا.
In this world,
في هذا العالم،
the one who understands me
الشخص الذي يفهمني
is Tao Shi.
هو تاو شي.
That day
ذلك اليوم
I fell gravely ill during my journey to the imperial examination.
لقد مرضت بشكل خطير أثناء رحلتي إلى الامتحان الإمبراطوري.
My life was in danger.
لقد كانت حياتي في خطر.
It was you, Brother Gao, a complete stranger,
لقد كنت أنت، الأخ جاو، غريبًا تمامًا،
who saved my life.
الذي أنقذ حياتي.
Your great kindness
لطفك العظيم
I, Tao Shi,
أنا، تاو شي،
will never forget.
لن أنسى أبدا.
If our positions were reversed,
لو انقلبت مواقفنا،
you wouldn't have left me to die either.
أنت أيضًا لم تتركني لأموت.
Besides,
بجانب،
wealth is easy to come by,
الثروة من السهل الحصول عليها،
but a kindred spirit is hard to find.
ولكن من الصعب العثور على روح متجانسة.
I've also gained a true friend,
لقد اكتسبت أيضًا صديقًا حقيقيًا،
so I'm only winning here.
لذلك أنا فقط الفائز هنا.
Ha!
ها!
Brother Gao,
الأخ قاو،
why don't we
لماذا لا نفعل ذلك
meet here on this day next year?
هل سنلتقي هنا في مثل هذا اليوم من العام القادم؟
I'll brew chrysanthemum wine
سأصنع نبيذ الأقحوان
and wait for you here.
و أنتظرك هنا.
The two of us
نحن الاثنان
can continue today's friendship.
يمكن أن تستمر الصداقة اليوم.
What do you say?
ماذا تقول؟
Wonderful!
رائع!
I was thinking the same.
كنت أفكر بنفس الشيء.
Our chrysanthemum wine appointment,
موعدنا مع نبيذ الأقحوان
it's a promise.
إنه وعد.
Brother Gao,
الأخ قاو،
the flowers have bloomed,
لقد تفتحت الزهور
and the wine is ready.
والنبيذ جاهز.
But I...
ولكن انا...
I'm afraid
انا خائف
I cannot keep our appointment.
لا أستطيع الالتزام بموعدنا.
In the next life,
في الحياة القادمة،
I will surely
انا سأفعل بالتأكيد
drink wine and admire chrysanthemums with you.
اشرب الخمر واستمتع بمشاهدة زهور الأقحوان معك.
Times have changed.
لقد تغيرت الأوقات.
You still haven't let go?
هل لم تتركه بعد؟
Brother Dongfang,
الأخ دونغفانغ،
this is the only lingering regret
هذا هو الندم الوحيد المتبقي
that keeps me in this world.
هذا ما يبقيني في هذا العالم.
If I take this pot of wine
إذا أخذت هذا القدر من النبيذ
and go through that door,
و اذهب من خلال هذا الباب،
I can travel to the world of a thousand years ago.
أستطيع أن أسافر إلى عالم مضى عليه ألف عام.
To find Brother Gao.
للعثور على الأخ جاو.
Wait!
انتظر!
Taoshi, you know
تاوشي، كما تعلم
what will happen if you go through this door.
ماذا سيحدث إذا دخلت من هذا الباب؟
He hasn't done anything wrong.
لم يفعل أي شيء خطأ.
He just wants to fulfill his promise.
إنه يريد فقط الوفاء بوعده.
Besides, isn't your monster inn
بالإضافة إلى ذلك، أليس نزل الوحش الخاص بك
supposed to help monsters resolve their obsessions?
من المفترض أن تساعد الوحوش في حل هواجسها؟
That's what you said.
هذا ما قلته.
Shut up.
اسكت.
What would a newcomer like you know?
ماذا يعرف الوافد الجديد مثلك؟
If you dare take one step outside,
إذا تجرأت على اتخاذ خطوة واحدة خارجًا،
you'll vanish into thin air before an incense stick burns out.
سوف تختفي في الهواء قبل أن تحترق عصا البخور.
You better think carefully.
من الأفضل أن تفكر جيدا.
Innkeeper.
صاحب النزل.
I'm not afraid.
أنا لست خائفا.
Even if I'm reduced to dust,
حتى لو تحولت إلى غبار،
I still have to go.
لا زال علي أن أذهب.
I'll take you there.
سوف آخذك إلى هناك.
Wait.
انتظر.
What is it now?
ما هو الآن؟
Weren't you planning to escape?
ألم تكن تخطط للهروب؟
What capacity are you taking him in?
ما هي القدرة التي تأخذه إليها؟
I've decided to stay.
لقد قررت البقاء.
Just temporarily though.
مؤقتا فقط.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Old friends depart one by one.
الأصدقاء القدامى يغادرون واحدا تلو الآخر.
Rivers flow on alone.
الأنهار تتدفق وحدها.
Suddenly seeing a visitor from dreams.
فجأة أرى زائرًا من الأحلام.
How many times will we grieve?
كم مرة سنحزن؟
My friend,
صديقي،
are you here to see the chrysanthemums?
هل أنت هنا لرؤية الأقحوان؟
I'm here on someone's behalf,
أنا هنا نيابة عن شخص ما،
to represent a friend,
لتمثيل صديق،
for an appointment.
للحصول على موعد.
Brother Gao,
الأخ قاو،
for our chrysanthemum wine appointment,
لموعدنا مع نبيذ الأقحوان،
I'm here.
أنا هنا.
Tao Shi.
تاو شي.
Tao Shi had no attachment
لم يكن لدى تاو شي أي ارتباط
to this bustling world.
إلى هذا العالم الصاخب.
He was simply unfortunate,
لقد كان سيئ الحظ بكل بساطة،
breaking his promise to meet you for chrysanthemum wine.
مخالفًا وعده بلقائك لتناول نبيذ الأقحوان.
But even so...
ولكن حتى مع ذلك...
He survived a thousand years through sheer will,
لقد نجا ألف عام من خلال إرادته الصرفة،
never forgetting his promise to you.
لن ينسى وعده لك أبدًا.
Today he finally comes to fulfill that promise.
واليوم يأتي أخيرا ليحقق هذا الوعد.
Please, Brother Gao,
من فضلك يا أخي جاو،
drink this cup of wine from Tao Shi.
اشرب هذا الكأس من النبيذ من تاو شي.
My friend.
صديقي.
Tao Shi is right here.
تاو شي موجود هنا.
Brother Gao.
الأخ قاو.
Just for one meeting,
فقط لاجتماع واحد
you'll turn to dust for this.
سوف تتحول إلى غبار بسبب هذا.
Is it worth it?
هل يستحق ذلك؟
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
you weren't trying to trap Tao Shi,
لم تكن تحاول الإيقاع بتاو شي،
but protecting him,
ولكن حمايته،
right?
يمين؟
Don't think so highly of me.
لا تفكر بي كثيرا.
I don't work overtime.
أنا لا أعمل وقتا إضافيا.
What's this?
ما هذا؟
You want to stay now?
هل تريد البقاء الآن؟
I think this job is quite interesting,
أعتقد أن هذه الوظيفة مثيرة للاهتمام للغاية،
like playing a murder mystery game.
مثل لعب لعبة جريمة قتل غامضة.
Once you agree,
بمجرد موافقتك،
there's no going back.
لا يوجد عودة .
Of course.
بالطبع.
What are you standing there for?
لماذا تقف هناك؟
Get to work.
اذهب إلى العمل.
I'm not finished yet.
لم أنتهي بعد.
I don't work overtime,
أنا لا أعمل ساعات إضافية،
especially night shifts.
وخاصة نوبات العمل الليلية.
Two days off per week,
يومين إجازة في الأسبوع
no working on holidays either.
لا أعمل في أيام العطل أيضًا.
Unless...
إلا إذا...
Triple pay.
الدفع الثلاثي.
No, five times the pay.
لا، خمسة أضعاف الأجر.
Keep talking,
استمر بالحديث
and I'll feed you to the demons.
وسأطعمك للشياطين.
Wait for me!
الانتظار لي!
Great benefits,
فوائد عظيمة
easy work,
عمل سهل
and a monster inn that helps guests resolve their obsessions.
ونزل وحشي يساعد الضيوف على حل هواجسهم.
You haven't joined some scam organization, have you?
لم تنضم إلى أي منظمة احتيال، أليس كذلك؟
What scam organization?
ما هي منظمة الاحتيال؟
To be precise,
ولكي نكون دقيقين،
they're special guests.
إنهم ضيوف مميزون.
Anyway, I've decided to stay and give it a try.
على أية حال، قررت البقاء ومحاولة ذلك.
Where did you say this place is?
أين قلت هذا المكان؟
I can't really explain that clearly.
لا أستطيع أن أشرح ذلك بوضوح.
A car will come to pick me up anyway.
ستأتي سيارة لأخذي على أية حال.
Is it that mysterious?
هل هو غامض إلى هذه الدرجة؟
Monster Inn.
نزل الوحش.
When can you take me there for a look?
متى يمكنك أن تأخذني هناك لإلقاء نظرة؟
You just stay put right here.
عليك فقط البقاء هنا.
Our place
مكاننا
doesn't hire people who wear glasses.
لا يتم توظيف الأشخاص الذين يرتدون النظارات.
At least leave me an address.
على الأقل اترك لي عنوانًا.
I might even refer some customers to you.
ربما أحيل بعض العملاء إليك.
Destined guests
الضيوف المقصودون
who hear the name of Monster Inn
من يسمع اسم Monster Inn
will naturally be invited to come.
سيتم دعوتك بشكل طبيعي للحضور.
Cheers!
هتافات!
Shangguan Feiye.
شانجوان فيي.
You really are a devil.
أنت شيطان حقا.
Have you always resolved customers' obsessions so violently?
هل كنت دائمًا تحل هواجس العملاء بهذه الطريقة العنيفة؟
The manager's business
عمل المدير
is none of your concern.
لا يهمك هذا الأمر.
Get back to work.
العودة إلى العمل.